https://stratemeyer.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to main contentHomePrivacy Policy Privacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://stratemeyer.org. It was written by James D. Keeline (www.keeline.com)What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.Contact formsIf you contact us through a contact form on the site, we will have whatever information you give (name, email) but we will not share this or sell this in anyway.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Who we share your data withNobody. We only have the normal analytics and cookies that all WordPress sites need to function and no more.
This does not keep personal data but does give us anonymous info like your country of origin, type of computer/browser, and when/how long you visited the site.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Share this:Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window) Subscribe to Blog via EmailEnter your email to receive notifications of new posts.
Email Address
Subscribe Sign up for newsletter24 Palmer Street PressCafepress Store: Tom Swift Merchandise Edward Stratemeyer 1862-1930 Wrote under his own name and several pseudonyms, including Arthur M. Winfield.Wrote several books as "Horatio Alger, Jr." after that author died, with permission of the estate.Wrote one book as "Oliver Optic" to complete a civil war series after that author died.His most popular series (that he wrote personally) are the Rover Boys and Dave Porter.Founded Syndicate in 1905 to hire ghostwriters to write books from his outlines.Most popular Syndicate series that he created are: Nancy Drew, the Hardy Boys, Tom Swift, the Bobbsey Twins and the Dana Girls.His daughters ran the Syndicate for 50 years after his death until it was purchased by Simon & Schuster.
Bobbsey TwinsBomba the Jungle BoyDana GirlsDon SturdyHardy BoysNancy DrewRalph of the RailroadTed ScottTom SwiftStratemeyer Syndicate Series Index James D. Keeline, Researcher and AuthorSeries Book Historian
